ugx-mods.com 2017-06-02

# Privacy Policy - UGX-Mods - UGX-Mods Confluence

Please note

By using [http://ugx-mods.com](http://ugx-mods.com/) ("this website") or any products or services provided by UGX-Mods (collectively "our products and services") you are agreeing to this document in its entirety.

We will make public notice about major changes to this document - but since this is a living document currently - we won't notify about any minor / trivial changes we make.

It's your responsibility to frequently check, read and understand it.

Short version

  * We collect anonymous statistics about your visit, like which of our pages you viewed.
  * Some 3rd parties like Facebook and Twitter may know you visited this website, if you use their services. We can’t control them but we don’t believe this knowledge poses any threat to you.
  * If you sign up with us we take great care to keep your information safe and we’ll never share it with others without your express permission.
  * We never share your data with 3rd parties except to help us deliver our own services.
  * For our full policy on cookies and 3rd party data, please refer to our Cookie Policy.

These are just the key points. If you need detail, keep reading. Remember, you are agreeing to this whole document, not just this summary!

* * *

## Detailed Privacy Policy

At UGX Mods, we collect and manage user data according to the following Privacy Policy, with the goal of incorporating our company values: transparency, accessibility, sanity, usability.

This document is part of UGX Mods' Terms of Service, and by using our products and services, you agree to the terms of this Privacy Policy and the Terms of Service.

 **Data Collected**

We collect anonymous data from every visitor of our products and services to monitor traffic and fix bugs.

For example, we collect information like web requests, the data sent in response to such requests, the Internet Protocol address, the browser type, the browser language, and a timestamp for the request.

We ask you to log in and provide certain personal information (such as your username and email address) in order to be able to save your profile and the documents and comments associated with it.

In order to enable these or any other login based features, we use cookies to store session information for your convenience.

You can block or delete cookies and still be able to use our products and services, although if you do you will then be asked for your username and password every time you log in to our products and services.

In order to take advantage of certain features of our products and services, you may also choose to provide us with other personal information, such as your picture or personal website, but your decision to utilize these features and provide such data will always be voluntary.

You are able to view, change and remove your data associated with your profile. Should you choose to delete your account, please contact us at [general@ugx-mods.com](mailto:general@ugx-mods.com) and we will follow up with such request as soon as possible.

Minors and children should not use our products and services. By using our products and services, you represent that you have the legal capacity to enter into a binding agreement.

 **Use of the Data**

We only use your personal information to provide you services or to communicate with you about our products and services.

With respect to any data you may choose to upload to our products and services, we take the privacy and confidentiality of such data seriously.

We encrypt all documents, and permanently delete any redacted edits you make to documents.

If you choose to make a document public, we recommend you redact any and all references to people and addresses, as we can't protect public data and we are not responsible for any violation of privacy law you may be liable for.

 **We do not share personal information you have provided to us without your consent** , unless:

  * doing so is appropriate to carry out your own request;
  * we believe it's needed to enforce our Terms of Service, or that is legally required;
  * we believe it's needed to detect, prevent or address fraud, security or technical issues;
  * otherwise protect our property, legal rights, or that of others.

Our products and services are operated from the United States. If you are using our products and services from outside the U.S., you agree to any processing of any personal information you provide us according to this policy.

UGX Mods may contact you, by email or other means. For example, UGX-Mods may send you promotional emails relating to our products and services or other third parties UGX Mods feels you would be interested in, or communicate with you about your use of our products and services. UGX Mods may also use technology to alert us via a confirmation email when you open an email from us. You can modify your email notification preferences by clicking the appropriate link included in the footer of email notifications. If you do not want to receive email from our products and services, please opt out of receiving emails at the bottom of any UGX Mods emails or by editing your profile preferences.

 **Sharing of Data**

We don't share your personal information with third parties. Only aggregated, anonymized data is periodically transmitted to external services to help us improve the UGX Mods Website and service.

We currently use Sovrn Ads Network, Google Analytics (traffic analysis, SEO optimization), [SparkPost](https://www.sparkpost.com/) (email delivery service).

We listed below what data these third parties extract exactly. Feel free to check out their own Privacy Policies to find out more.

  * Google Analytics: anonymous (ad serving domains, browser type, demographics, language settings, page views, time/date), pseudonymous (IP address)
  * SparkPost: <https://www.sparkpost.com/policies>
  * Sovrn collects anonymous site visit data.
  * Sovrn collects only anonymous information unless a reader chooses to submit personal information to Sovrn.
  * Users may opt out of this anonymous data collection by installing the Lijit “opt-out” cookie. [Click here](http://info.evidon.com/pub_info/2672?v=1&nt=0&nw=false) to install this cookie.
  * Sovrn’s privacy policy can be reviewed at the following location: <https://www.sovrn.com/privacy-policy/>

We also use social buttons provided by services like Twitter, Google+ and Facebook.

Your use of these third party services is entirely optional. We are not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices of these third party services, and you are responsible for reading and understanding those third party services’ privacy policies.

We employ and contract with people and other entities that perform certain tasks on our behalf and who are under our control (our “Agents”). We may need to share personal information with our Agents in order to provide products or services to you. Unless we tell you differently, our Agents do not have any right to use Personal Information or other information we share with them beyond what is necessary to assist us. You hereby consent to our sharing of Personal Information with our Agents.

We may choose to buy or sell assets. In these types of transactions, user information is typically one of the transferred business assets. Moreover, if we, or substantially all of our assets, were acquired, or if we go out of business or enter bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of us or our assets may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

These third parties may also store cookies on your machine. Please refer to our Cookie Policy for a full description of our policy on cookies.  
By agreeing to this Privacy Policy you have also agreed to our Cookie Policy.

 **Changes to the Privacy Policy**

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is used.  
If we make major changes in the way we collect or use information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our products and services or sending you an email.  
A user is bound by any changes to the Privacy Policy when they use our products and services after such changes have been first posted.

 **Questions?**

Should you have any question or concern, please [contact us](https://jira.ugx-mods.com/servicedesk/customer/portal/6).
